<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hisab</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_header_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="user_shared_preef">user_detail</string>
    <string name="shared_pref_name">User_name</string>
    <string name="default_username">User</string>
    <string name="shared_pref_number">User_number</string>
    <string name="default_usernumber">1234567890</string>
    <string name="dp_temp_name">dp_crop.jpg</string>
    <string name="dp_temp_uncrop_name">dp.jpg</string>
    <string name="user_number_info">Number won\'t be shared. It will only be used when friend shares account status.</string>

    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_pending">Pending</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_settled">Settled</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_analysis">E-Analysis</string>
    <string name="shared_transition_person_name">sharedPersonName</string>

    <string-array name="category_list">
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Education</item>
        <item>Party</item>
        <item>Movie</item>
        <item>Misc</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="SENT_TOKEN_TO_SERVER">token_done</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="pending_rem">pendingRem</string>
    <string name="not_sound">notSound</string>
    <string name="not_vibrate">notVibrate</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_send_reminder">Send Reminder</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_sync_pending">Sync Pending</string>
    <string name="gcm_rec_req_bunlde_userid">UserID</string>
    <string name="gcm_rec_req_bunlde_type">type</string>
    <string name="gcm_rec_req_bunlde_accept">RequestAccepted</string>


    <!-- FAQ -->

    <string-array name="faq_question">
        <item>What is Hisab?</item>
        <item>What is shown in the First Screen</item>
        <item>What are the options in Navigation Menu</item>
        <item>What is shown in Pending Section</item>
        <item>What is shown in Settled Section</item>
        <item>What is shown in Analysis Section</item>
        <item>What is Send Reminder?</item>
        <item>What is Sync Pending?</item>
        <item>Does My Transactions are visible to anyone?</item>
        <item>How to add new Transaction</item>
        <item>Where Can I see My Profile?</item>
        <item>How Do I change my DP?</item>
        <item>How Do I edit my Account detail?</item>
        <item>What is this Points</item>
        <item>What is Group?</item>
        <item>How to Create a Group?</item>
        <item>Type Of Group?</item>
        <item>How can I add new member in Group</item>
        <item>How can I delete a member from a Group</item>
        <item>How can I delete a Group</item>
        <item>How can I assign a new Admin to Group</item>
        <item>What are the admin\'s right?</item>
        <item>Who can see my question?</item>
        <item>Can I answer any questions?</item>
        <item>How Many Time can I answer a Question?</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_answer">
        <item>Ask It is social platform which allows it user to ask for opinions of people around the globe
            \nIt also provide way to ask questions to yours friends
            \nAsk It gives a platform to its users to share their opinions on questions asked by people all around globe.
        </item>
        <item>The 3 category on main screen categorizes the type of question you can see.
            \nRead the subsequent questions to know what they mean.
        </item>
        <item>Feed Section shows the question asked by the people you follow.
            \nNote that if a person whom you follow asks a private question( Wait! what is a private question? It is explained below) then it won\'t be visible in feeds
            \nbut that question an be visible in Personal section if that question is asked to you.
            \nOne more thing Question in Feed Section are in Chronological Order.
        </item>
        <item>Trending Section shows the most discussed question in the community.
            \nIt is sorted based on the number of votes and the time it was asked
        </item>
        <item>Personal Section include private question asked for you.
            \nThese questions will never will shown either in Feed or Trending section
        </item>
        <item>User just simply need to click on (+) button  to ask a question.
            \nThere are several steps once you click the button, they are:
            \n1) Select type of question.(Types are explained below)
            \n2) Write your question and give suitable options. At least 2 options are needed.
            \n3) Select Category of question
            \n4) Enter User-Id or select group if you want to make the question private. Otherwise leave it blank.
        </item>
        <item>Based on people who should see your question, questions are of two type described below</item>
        <item>General Question is one which is not for a specific user or group of user.
            \nThis question can be viewed by anyone in community and any one can answer it
        </item>
        <item>Private question are the one which are for a specific user or a group of users.
            \nThis question can be viewed by only  those people whom you choose while posting question.
        </item>
        <item>Just enter the User-Id(s) or select a group in private section while posting question to make it private.</item>
        <item>Category is just to show your voters in which context is this question asked.
            \nIt is optional as well as multiple category can be selected.
        </item>
        <item>Long press the Question to delete it</item>
        <item>Long press the Question to report it
            \nAfter reporting our team will check it and if question does not satisfy our terms it would be deleted.
        </item>
        <item>To view your profile follow the step:
            \n1) Click the menu button(3 dots) on Main Screen
            \n2) Click on the First Option(Showing your user id) to see your profile.
        </item>
        <item>By clicking on the existing DP</item>
        <item>By clicking edit button</item>
        <item>Points shows how active you are in community. More Point More Active!
            \nYou get 2 Points for a question
            \n And 1 Point for answer.
        </item>
        <item>Group is a collection of user id.
            \nMaking group helps you to add many people as target for your question without typing their user id again.
        </item>
        <item>to Create group, go through following steps:
            \n1) Go to your profile
            \n2) Click on Groups
            \n3) The first option there , "New Group" , will help you to make group.
            \n4) Once you click that button, you need to enter Group Name, User- ID of member and type of group.
        </item>
        <item>There are 3 type of groups:
            \n1) Default Group: In such group, any user can send request to join your group, but only admin will have right to add the user.
            \n2) Strict Group: No user can send a join request.
            \n3) Open Group: Any user can join group without admin\'s permission
        </item>
        <item>
            You can only add new member if You are a admin of that Group.
            \n To add a member long click on the group name and a pop upp will prompt you to add member
        </item>
        <item>
            You can only delete a member if You are a admin of that Group.
            \n To delete a member click on the group name.
            \n In the group member list long click on the user name and a pop upp will prompt you to delete that member
        </item>
        <item>
            You can only delete a group only if You are a admin of that Group.
            \n To delete your group long click on the group name and a pop upp will prompt you to delete group
            \nIf you are not admin but you want to leave group click the leave button
        </item>
        <item>
            You can assign a new admin only if You are a admin of that Group.
            \n To assign a admin click on the group name.
            \n In the group member list long click on the user name and a pop upp will prompt you to make that member admin
        </item>
        <item>
            Admin can add member, remove member and make new Admin
        </item>
        <item>If the question is private, It can only be viewed by targeted user, otherwise it will be viewed by all</item>
        <item>You can answer any question visible to you</item>
        <item>One user can answer a question only once</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
